pyz.am 2016-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Pyzam

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Pyz.am collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from visitors to http://pyz.am and any subpages collected referred to as the (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Pyz.am.

**  
Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Personal Identifiable Information**

We may collect personal identifiable information from visitors in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when visitors view any portion of the Site, enter information into any contact forms, use any of the products or services offered on the Site, and other activities, services, features or resources we make available on the Site. Visitors may be asked for name, email address, and other information at various times as needed to give the intended user experience.

We will collect personal information from visitors only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Visitors can always refuse to supply personal information, although it may limit their ability to utilize various portions of the Site.

**Non-Personal Identifiable Information**

We collect non-personal identification information about visitors whenever they interact with our Site. This information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about visitors’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**How we use collected information**

Pyz.am collects and uses visitor’s personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize user experience and offer personalized content
  * Aggregated information is used to understand how our visitors as a group use the services and resources provided on pyz.am

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of all information and data stored in association with the Site.

**Sharing your information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent personally identifiable visitor information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any specific individual regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we detect are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Pyz.am reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, the revision date below will be updated as well. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically to stay informed regarding any changes.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://pyz.am/tos/). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

support@pyzam.com

_Last revised: 5/4/16_
